Hey guys, we're back in
Germany and we're going out now.   Did
you have a
fever yesterday, or already today?
I had a fever yesterday, right now it's around
38-36 something, but nothing's stopping me from going out
today.
I just have to go out today.  We're
going outside now and we're going to do our outfits
together, and she has to straighten her hair
now, and mine is already
straight.  I missed my straight hair so much, guys
.
I miss it too,
and yeah, bye guys, see you later.  As you
know, I didn't wear that much makeup in Italy
.  I do
n't know if I have some kind of
trauma from
who did my makeup last time, but
we've
done a lot today, I'd say, right?
I definitely don't know what I'm going to wear
, but we'll definitely look into that soon
.  I just applied hair oil to
my hair, and yeah, guys,
ignore my room.  It's really not
tidy.  I just put on
a skirt from Hollister.
Top, no idea.  From where?  So
probably New Yorker or something, and
I'll wear slippers and I think
my Balenzager bag.  I've
decided to go with BB after all, because Z was a
bit of a mess.